[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What system accounts for approximately 16% of the human body?",
        "answer": "Integumentary system"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which system is comprised of 206 individual organs?",
        "answer": "Skeletal system"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which system is comprised of smooth, voluntary, and cardiac tissues?",
        "answer": "Muscular system"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which system asts like the nervous system, but with slower reaction time and longer-lasting effects?",
        "answer": "Endocrine system"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which system is a closed circuit whose main function is transportation through a network of vessels?",
        "answer": "Cardiovascular system"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which system transports a whitish, watery fluid called lymph?",
        "answer": "Lymphatic system"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which system produces waste in the kidney that moves to the ureters, and is stored in the urinary bladder?",
        "answer": "Urinary system"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which system funtions as a means to rid the body of carbon dioxide?",
        "answer": "Respiratory system"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which system includes both the teeth and the pharynx?",
        "answer": "Digestive system"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What orhan is considered the female gonads?",
        "answer": "Ovaries"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which type of membrane is found in closed cavities in the body?",
        "answer": "Serous membranes"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is the purpose of the synergist in movement?",
        "answer": "Add support to the contracting prime mover"
    }
]
